{
    "id": "602bdfaf850b4fb689cd8323ee85e96c",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………….. the girl tried her best, she could not get the first rank.",
            "description": "We use although to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "As though",
                "As if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3071aed58bcd4240b64d2250e932a064"
        },
        {
            "question": "The moon …………………….. the stars gives light at night.",
            "description": "As well as is similar to both…and. The above can also be expressed as ‘Both the moon and the stars give light at night.’",
            "answers": [
                "both and",
                "as well",
                "as well as",
                "also"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "86d82b213bb74343b71260d72c265ca0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He treated me ………………………….. he had not met me before.",
            "description": "We use as if and as though to say what a situation seems like.",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "as though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "553ce340225f431db0f0d946dfa676ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "He screamed ………………………….. he had seen a ghost.",
            "description": "We use as if to say what a situation seems like.",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "as",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d65347dddf944c52b0b10809cf3eafcb"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… he felt tired, he sat down to rest.",
            "description": "As can indicate the reason for something. It is similar to because.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "If",
                "As if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "39038e6b1dec45579f32b4dcf301dc34"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was ……………………… much noise for me to enjoy the film.",
            "description": "There was a lot of noise. I could not enjoy the film. We can express the same idea using too ….to.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cdd688e0d5b343baa5f6250f6bfbbd47"
        },
        {
            "question": "He borrowed some money from his friends ……………………….. he could buy a car.",
            "description": "We use so that to indicate purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "such that",
                "so as to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "254bc9d2f5c04f13ba66420e00b7ae1b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He offered his daughter a prize ……………………………. she might work hard.",
            "description": "We use so that to indicate purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "such that",
                "in order to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "72faffa9f676484fb408c07be7ac82ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "The famine was ………………………… severe …………………… very few people survived.",
            "description": "We use so that to indicate the purpose or result.",
            "answers": [
                "so...that",
                "such...as",
                "such...that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dec532ff537b4dc8826b9bb82946e3ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ……………………….. a hot day that I couldn’t do any work.",
            "description": "Such that can mean to such an extent.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fd0fd304cb2b4a78900effd2a738237e"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. I drop this glass, it will break.",
            "description": "We use ‘if’ to express a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Whether",
                "As"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cf648f5fc61f4220b2d276ec3dfbc192"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must …………………………… complete your work or get someone else to complete it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "nor"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "758228191698465c8fdd10c71c4eb41a"
        }
    ]
}